{"data":[{"question":"My father to Ben: \"I'm sure I saw you here last week.\"     -> My father told Ben .......................","answer":"he was sure he had seen him there the previous week","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"Betty: \"If I knew the answer, I would tell you.\"     -> Betty assured me that ........................","answer":"if she knew the answer she would tell me","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"Tomorrow at five o'clock I'll be sitting on the train to Glasgow - he said.     -> He told her ................................................the train to Glasgow","answer":"that the next day at five o'clock he would be sitting on","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"Mr Jones to us: \"I will teach you how to do research on the Web.\"     -> Mr Jones informed us ........................to do research on the Web.","answer":"he would teach us how","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"My brother: \"I don't forget things that I like.''     -> My brother said ............................","answer":"he didn't forget things that he liked","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"Miss Claymore: \"One month ago I warned you to study for that test.\"     -> Miss Claymore reminded us ......................................for that test.","answer":"that before one month she had warned us to study","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"\"If you give me some money, I'll help you\" - said the man.     -> The man said to Betty that ..................................","answer":"if she gave him the money, he would help her.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"Dave: \"I was outside the classroom during break but I saw a group of my colleagues inside the room.\"     -> Dave said .........................................................a group of my colleagues inside the room.","answer":"he was outside the classroom during the break but he had seen","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"Patricia: \"I'm sorry I haven't told anyone the truth until now.'     -> Patriciacried ...................................................","answer":"she was sorry she hadn't told anyone the truth until then","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"Mrs Wilson: \"No one has ever spoken to me like this before.\"     -> Mrs Wilson announced ........................................","answer":"no one had ever spoken to her like that before","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"}]}